<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Foxkeh&apos;s Blog (foxkeh.com)</title>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/</link>
<description>Spread Firefox with Foxkeh, a cute mascot born in Japan!</description>
<language>en</language>
<copyright>Copyright (C) 2011 Mozilla Japan. All rights reserved.</copyright>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 09:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>

<item>
<title>Notice To Readers</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p>Unfortunately we will temporarily stop updating Foxkeh.com.</p><p>However, Foxkeh's monthly wallpapers are still available from <a href="http://foxkeh.jp/downloads/wallpapers/">Foxkeh.jp</a>. "2009 年 12 月" means "December 2009", "2010 年 1 月" means "January 2010" and so on. You can find several types of wallpapers:</p><p>* "カレンダー付き (日曜始まり・休日表示あり)" means "With calendar starts on Sundays, Japanese National Holidays indicated"<br />* "カレンダー付き (日曜始まり・休日表示なし)" means "With calendar starts on Sundays, no holidays indicated"<br />* "カレンダー付き (月曜始まり・休日表示なし)" means "With calendar starts on Mondays, no holidays indicated"<br />* "カレンダーなし" means "Without calendar"<br />* "携帯サイズ" is sized for Japanese mobile phones</p><p>Sorry for any inconvenience, and thank you again for your continuous support for Firefox and Foxkeh!<br /></p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/5066/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/5066/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, October 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p>We're already halfway into October, so please let us apologize for the delayed note. <a href="http://foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200910/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a><a href="http://foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">Foxkeh's October wallpaper</a> is now available.  This month, Foxkeh is feasting on some fall fruits and may have eaten a bit more than he should have.  If Foxkeh gets too fat, he'll start looking like a racoon! Foxkeh, please don't eat too much =^_^=.</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4762/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4762/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh</category><category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 17:10:02 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh&apos;s 3rd birthday, September 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200909/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a>Foxkeh, who was born on September 1st, 2006, is now 3 years old! Before we even knew it, Foxkeh had <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">32 wallpapers</a> created for him, and this <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">33rd wallpaper</a> celebrates Foxkeh's third birthday.  Please remember, as long as you are not using Foxkeh for commercial profit, and you credit Mozilla, you're free to use Foxkeh in your own way.  The design of Foxkeh seems pretty simple at first, but to draw Foxkeh yourself is harder than it looks. The staff of Mozilla Japan tried to draw Foxkeh but he ended up looking like a cat or a dog, not like the red panda that he is.  If you are drawing your own Foxkeh, please feel free to use the <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/">Foxkeh images and body parts</a> that are distributed on the <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/">download page</a>.  Happy birthday to Foxkeh and thank you to everyone who loves him and shares him with your friends and family.  Foxkeh appreciates your love.]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4677/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4677/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh</category><category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 18:59:52 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, August 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200908/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> <a href="http://foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">Foxkeh's wallpapers</a> for August are available for download. Enjoy your summer vacation with Foxkeh on the beach of Shiretoko!</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4517/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4517/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2009 00:22:17 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, July 2009 </title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p>The <a href="http://foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200907/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" />July Foxkeh wallpapers</a> have been released a few days ago.  Apologies for the delay as we were very busy with the launch of <a href="http://www.mozilla.com/en-US/firefox/upgrade.html?from=getfirefox">Firefox 3.5</a> recently.  Have you downloaded your copy?<p>This month Foxkeh is hiking in the Shiretoko National Park.  Have you had a chance to <a href="http://www.discovershiretoko.org/en/campaign/">create a banner</a> to promote Shiretoko and Firefox?  If not, here's your chance.  You can see everyone participating in the campaign at the <a href="http://www.interforest.org/">InterFORest</a> site. Please consider <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4230/">joining Foxkeh to support</a> both the efforts of the non-profit Shiretoko Nature Foundation as well as the non-profit Mozilla Foundation.<br /></p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4393/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4393/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 21:55:33 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Discover Shiretoko</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.discovershiretoko.org/en/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/img/discover-shiretoko-home-thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0pt 0pt 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> </p><p>The official release of Firefox 3.5 is almost here.</p><p>At Mozilla Japan, we have been planning a project to promote the new version of Firefox.  Today we have started the <a href="http://www.discovershiretoko.org/en/">Discover Shiretoko</a> campaign along with the non-profit <a href="http://www.shiretoko.or.jp/en/">Shiretoko Nature Foundation</a> of Hokkaido, Japan.</p><p>As some of you may know, each version of Firefox has a code-name that is the name of a national park. The code name for Firefox 3.5 is "Shiretoko" which is taken from the name of the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shiretoko_National_Park">Shiretoko National Park</a> in Northern Japan.</p><p>In addition to promoting this new version of Firefox, we wanted to also take this opportunity to co-promote the <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/tags/shiretoko/">beautiful natural forests of Shiretoko</a>, Hokkaido which were given <a href="http://whc.unesco.org/en/news/134">UNESCO World Heritage status</a> in 2005.  </p><p>Why is Mozilla collaborating with a non-profit nature conservancy organization?  In fact Mozilla and this organization have a number of common goals and you can read <a href="http://www.discovershiretoko.org/en/">4 stores about Firefox and Shiretoko</a> at the Discover Shiretoko site.</p><div style="text-align: center;"><strong><a href="http://www.discovershiretoko.org/en/">Discover Shiretoko</a></strong></div><p>In addition, in order to get more people to know about both the Shiretoko national park as well as the new version of Firefox, we've started a web banner campaign called "tree banner."  This banner uses the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canvas_%28HTML_element%29">Canvas</a> element to grow a "virtual tree" on your site.</p><div style="text-align: center;"><strong><a href="http://www.interforest.org/">interFORest</a></strong></div><p>In addition you can see all of the other people who have registered at Discover Shiretoko to grow a virtual tree on their own site at the <a href="http://www.interforest.org/">interFORest site</a> which shows all of the virtual trees growing on a virtual map of the Shiretoko peninsula. </p><p><a href="http://www.interforest.org/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/img/discover-shiretoko-interforest-thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0pt 0pt 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a></p><p>For more details on the banner campaign, please go to the <a href="http://www.discovershiretoko.org/en/campaign/">Banner Campaign site</a> at Discover Shiretoko.</p><p>To see a map of all the participating websites, please go to the <a href="http://www.interforest.org/">interFORest site</a>.</p><p>We hope you will support both Firefox 3.5 and Shiretoko with these banners on your website or blog.</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4230/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4230/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 21:16:05 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, June 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200906/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0pt 0pt 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> Foxkeh's <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">wallpapers</a> for June are available for download. Shiretoko finally welcomes a late cherry blossom season. Foxkeh is taking a little break under cherry trees while he's hiking. The blossoms in full bloom appear similar to the snowscape in Shiretoko. Be careful not to burn your backpack with your tail flame, Foxkeh!</p><p><strong>Update</strong>: We have corrected calendars starting on Mondays. Thanks Olly!</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4135/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4135/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 21:30:48 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, May 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p>Welcome to new visitors from <a href="http://lifehacker.com/5239186/monthly-firefox+themed-wallpapers-with-embedded-calendars">Lifehacker: Monthly Firefox-Themed Wallpapers with Embedded Calendars</a>.<br /><p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200905/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0pt 0pt 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a><br />Apologies for the delay as Foxkeh was out on vacation during <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Golden_Week_%28Japan%29">Golden Week</a>. This month's <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">wallpaper</a> features the spring blooming <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lysichiton">Lysichiton</a> which is native to the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shiretoko_National_Park">Shiretoko National Park</a>. Did you know that Shiretoko is also the code-name for the upcoming <a href="https://wiki.mozilla.org/Firefox3.1">Firefox 3.5 browser</a>? Foxkeh is enjoying the spring rays of sunshine and is frolicking in the park with a butterfly. Now that the long winter has ended and spring has arrived in Shiretoko, Foxkeh is eagerly looking forward to playing in the park. Please download the <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">May 2009 Foxkeh wallpaper</a> and share it with friends.</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4056/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/4056/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh</category><category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 20:51:04 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, April 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200904/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0pt 0pt 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> Foxkeh is back for April with a <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">wallpaper</a> that marks the beginning of spring. Foxkeh is seen running around <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shiretoko_National_Park">Shiretoko National Park</a> when some of the last melting snow lands on his head. Spring has finally come to Shiretoko!</p><p>PS: This month we put a tree in the upper-right and placed a calendar in the middle following some of the feedback from Mac users. If this works well for everyone we'll continue to place it in the middle. We'd love to hear your comments!</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3955/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3955/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 18:16:56 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, March 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200903/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0pt 0pt 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> The <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">Foxkeh Wallpapers</a> for March are here (a few days late, our apologies.) This month, Foxkeh is at the Northernmost tip of Japan, at Japan's <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shiretoko_National_Park">Shiretoko National Park</a>. Foxkeh is floating on drift ice that has floated down from Siberia and is focused on fishing but we're a bit worried that his flaming tail may melt his piece of ice? In 2009, Mozilla will release a new version of Firefox code-named "<a href="https://wiki.mozilla.org/Firefox3.1">Shiretoko</a>" and thus starting this month the wallpapers will share the theme of "Shiretoko." I wonder what next month Foxkeh will be doing in Shiretoko?</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3851/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3851/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 17:51:27 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, February 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200902/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">The February 2009 Foxkeh wallpapers</a> have arrived. This month Foxkeh is looking at and thinking about the Earth. Is Foxkeh's larger-than-normal fire tail a sign of his commitment to the upcoming release of Firefox 3.1? You may know that the codename for Firefox 3.1 is '<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shiretoko_National_Park">Shiretoko</a>', a famous national park in Japan, and is the first Japanese code-name for Firefox. Foxkeh, being from Japan, is in high spirits for this upcoming new browser.  What will Foxkeh be doing next month?]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3706/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3706/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 12:21:27 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, January 2009</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200901/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> Happy new year from Foxkeh and Mozilla!  Thank you for taking interest in Foxkeh and sharing his wallpapers and blog parts on your computer desktops and blogs.  This month <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">Foxkeh is playing in the snow</a> trying to make a snowman.  If you have some illustration software, please add to the rest of the snowman for Foxkeh and link to us the image in the comments.  We look forward to seeing what kind of snowman you would create for Foxkeh.]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3604/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3604/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 01:32:26 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, December 2008 </title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p></p><p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200812/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> Happy winter! The <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">December Foxkeh wallpapers</a> have arrived.This month, Foxkeh is riding a sleigh.  I hope he knows how to steer it properly. This year Foxkeh has tried so many different sports, but since he's quite athletic and has great balance, we haven't worried too much. This month's wallpaper is the last for 2008.  Next year we plan to continue the wallpapers and we'll choose a different theme.  If you have any ideas for themes for next year's wallpapers, please leave us a comment. We all look forward to more Foxkeh in 2009!]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3481/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3481/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 22:13:01 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, November 2008</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://foxkeh.jp/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200811/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> <p>Please let us apologize for the delayed announcement.  The <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">November Foxkeh wallpapers</a> are now available. </p><p>This month, the theme is ice hockey, which is a winter sport most popular in North America. As it is sometimes called a "martial art on ice" will Foxkeh be ok in this rough-and-tumble sport?  Although Foxkeh is not wearing his helmet in this image, of course in a real game he would wear his helmet for safety.  Also Foxkeh can use his flaming tail to block attacks, so he would be a formidable opponent.</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3335/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3335/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh</category><category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 17:48:36 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foxkeh wallpapers, October 2008</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/"><img src="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/200810/thumb.png" alt="" style="margin: 0 0 1em 1em; float: right;" /></a> The weather has turned cool for fall in Tokyo.  How is the weather where you are?  This October, <a href="http://www.foxkeh.com/downloads/wallpapers/">Foxkeh is trying skydiving</a>. Skydiving must feel like a nice stroll in the woods with the crisp autumn air... wait, it's probably not quite like that :).  After Foxkeh lands on the ground, we'll ask him what his impressions of skydiving are. Have you been skydiving?  Please tell us what it feels like if you have experienced it yourself.</p>]]>

</description>
<link>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3184/</link>
<guid>http://www.foxkeh.com/blog/3184/</guid>
<category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Foxkeh Wallpapers</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 19:09:17 -0800</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
